Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/kieu-thanh-truc-nguyen-347b6819a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Systems Analysis Flow Charts Use Cases

Certifications

EF SET English Certificate 63/100 (C1 Advanced)

Honors-Awards

Excellent Marketing Department Award 2021

Kieu Thanh Truc Nguyen

Information Technology Business Analyst District 7, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

I have more than five years experience in business administration. My core competency is as a project manager, but I am able to adapt easily to new working environments and tasks given. In addition, I have good interpersonal skills that are useful when working with diverse populations, such as; staff members/students of different ages, professionals from different countries, etc. With this said, the knowledge gained from these experiences would definitely be an asset to any organisation

Experience

FPT Software
Information Technology Business Analyst
June 2023 - Present (1 year 10 months)

AGG

Operations Manager April 2022 - April 2023 (1 year 1 month) Landmark 1, 720A Dien Bien Phu, Binh Thanh District

Assure Global Group Senior Business Analyst April 2022 - April 2023 (1 year 1 month)

Prudential Vietnam Assurance Private Ltd. Customer Portfolio Senior Specialist October 2021 - April 2022 (7 months)

- -In charge of all data analysis of PRURewards customers' portfolio, including VIPs movement, VIP expired point, redemption behavior,...;
- -Manage PruGuard codes (PRG247) in Q4 to contribute up to 1k policies issued per month;
- -Extract data and report PRURewards campaigns: 22nd Birthday Prudential, 4 days Peak hour, 20/10, 20/11, Chrismast Eve, 14/2, 8/3 events,...;

- -In charge of system enhancement: PRUOnline, PRURewards and Communication engine by testing system to assure tools run effectively and efficiently;
- -Create PRUOnline, PRURewards and Communication system documents for end users;
- -Reach totally 98% VIP redemption in total of nearly 190k VIP customers;
- -Reach 25% self redemption out of nearly 270k redeem transactions.

CÔNG TY CỔ PHẦN TẬP ĐOÀN TÁO KIM CƯƠNG

Data Analyst

September 2020 - November 2021 (1 year 3 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- -Establish the specific goals, objectives and opportunities of kindergarten's market;
- -Analyze and visualize statistics to interpret the data set for the reports;
- -Design customer, supplier and investor journeys using experience and provided data led thinking in order to standardize customer, supplier, investor process and increase efficiency;
- -Save 50% of time consuming on customer service by embracing customer life time value:
- -Provide customer insight to help BD Department to maintain 80% of existing customers as well as approach new customer segmentation;
- -Maintain 85% of customer's satisfactions.

MAPA

Assistant Manager

March 2020 - September 2020 (7 months)

Vietnam

- -Undertake detailed ongoing analysis of marketing campaigns to ensure targets are met;
- -Assist in the production of ongoing competitor analysis and reporting, with particular reference to pricing, presentation and promotions;
- -Collaborates with the relevant partners and stakeholders to ensure project and operational performances are met;
- -Build supporting information material and market research for campaign;
- -Connect teachers and student through Platform.

Be Group JSC

Driver Community Assistant Manager October 2018 - January 2020 (1 year 4 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- -Recruit more than 60,000 drivers to establish ride hailing service, which reached 80% target of driver recruitment;
- -Work with related departments such as Sales, PR and Marketing Department to determine domestic consumption drive;
- -Create reports, graphs, and data visualization in order to manage and allocate drivers;
- -Achieved 85% drivers' satisfaction of driver caring by getting feedbacks from drivers;
- -Technological driver is prime and respected campaign 2019 is known as Tay Lai Vang competition 2019;
- -Increase drivers' advocacy for Brand in Driver Community as well as Brand Awareness;
- -Maintain nearly 60,000 drivers loyalty to the firm;

University of Greenwich Student Advisor August 2017 - June 2018 (11 months)

142 Pham Phu Thu, Quan 6

- -Consult parents and grade-12-students in choosing majors in college;
- -Orient student's passionate and career path;
- -Track the progress of selling and support customers' demand;
- -Serve around 100 students per day via frequent social media;
- -Report weekly sales performance to sales lead.

Dang Gia Trang Company Marketing Executive June 2016 - March 2017 (10 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- -Research the demand of organic fertilizer usages in market;
- -Have SEO experience in organic fertilizer categories;
- -Manage Facebook fan page experience and increase brand awareness;
- -Research and analysis competitors' product;
- -Serve and take care over 10 customers per day.

Education

University of Greenwich

Bachelor's degree, Business Administration and Management,

General · (2014 - 2018)